CARSON KEY

Software Engineer

Portfolio: https://carsonkey.dev/ Bend, Oregon carson@kev.family

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/carson-key-720a04b6/ Github: https://github.com/Carson-Key/

To gain more experience working on large scale and small scale projects alike to advance my personal growth and knowledge. Applying experience and knowledge gained to a full-time career in Software Engineering.

Professional Experience

June 2021 - Present

Temp Tech Consultant

Oregon State University-Cascades, Bend, Oregon

- · Helping prepare all classrooms for a return to in person classes (this was in 2021, durning the pandemic)
- Helping train and orientate two new hires to the Cascades team
- $\bullet \ \ \text{Getting all computers imaged ready for the school year, this ranged form faculty computers to lab}$
- Developing miscellaneous software for the Cascades IT team
- Developing a React based dashboard for the director of OSU main campus at Corvallis to display statuses of various products

February 2018 -June 2021

IT Student Worker

Oregon State University-Cascades, Bend, Oregon

- Collect data and modify configs on various servers
- Troubleshoot and fix user technology issues which ranged from faculty/staff compiters to classroom
- · Preping all technology ready for the school year
- · Odd tech II tasks

July 2019 - January 2020

Developer Intern

Redhawk Network Security, LLC, Bend, Oregon

- · Maintain legacy software
- · PHP development
- Add new features to legacy code
- Start development on a React based account creation wizard

June 2018 -

September 2018

Developer Intern

CBT Nuggets, Bend, Oregon

- Developing a React based website to be used in the QA engineer interview process
- Developing a React based dashboard addon to display test automation statistics

References

Tania Mahood | Director of IT at OSU -Cascades

Evan Randall | Equipment Specialist at OSU-Cascades

Tyler Hardison | CTO at Redhawk Network Security

Ryan Sullivan | Team Leader/QA Engineer at Cbr Nuggets

Kathie Quick | Math Department Head and CS Teacher at Summit High School

Sarah Warsow | Activities Director at Summit High School

Greig Thompson | AP CS and Science Teacher at Summit High School

Education

Bachelor of Science in Software

Engineering

Oregon State University-Cascades at Bend, Oregon | September 2017 - June 2021

High School Honors Diploma Summit High School at Bend, Oregon |

Key Skills

2013 - 2017

Troubleshooting/Debugging

Swift Programming Language

Code Design (Software Engineering)

